Rutuja Erande

Batchelor Of Computer Application

Contact

Address

Pune, India 411033

Phone

09284880235

E-mail

rutujaerande12@gmail.com

WWW

https://bold.pro/my/rutujaerande/693

Skills

Good customer service

Administrative support

Accounting systems and software

Rapid data entry skills

Ledger and balance sheet competency

Financial services

Cash Handling

Banking

Languages

Marathi

Hindi

English

Secure a responsible position in account management and serve as an account representative sharing my breadth of experience and abilities e ecting mutual employee and employer growth and success. Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals.

Work History

2015-01 -2019-01 Indrayani Co-Operative bank Ltd

- I worked all banking related activities
- Like account opening-closing,FD related work,handling cash,etc.

2011-01 -2013-01 Rajguru Nagar Co-Operative bank Ltd

- I worked all banking related activities
- Like account opening-closing,FD related work,etc.

Education

2010-01

Batchelor Of Computer Applications

Pune University

GPA: 53.66

Maharashtra Board

Accomplishments

• Passing Year - 2006

• Grades: 49.56

- Jana Prabhodini Navanagar Vidyalaya, Nigdi, Pune
- SSC
- Passing Year 2004
- Grades: 43.44
- PROJECTS
- Project Details
- Handling academic projects like super market billing system

Contact: 9284880238

• Email: rutujaerande12@gmail.com

• DOB: 12/11/1988